Guide to the Burke Centre Conservator newsletter collection, 1977-1993
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Burke Centre Conservator newsletter collection
1977-1993
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Robert P. Clark
C0167
2 linear feet (4 boxes)
The Burke Centre Conservator newsletter collection documents the monthly activities of Burke Centre, such as elections, programs and festivals.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Robert P. Clark in June 1993.
Historical Information
Burke is a part of Fairfax County in Northern Virginia. The area was named after Silas Burke a resident of the area during the nineteenth century. Silas Burke was a farmer and local politician whose house still stands in Burke. Burke Centre is one of the largest developments within Burke which is managed by the Burke Centre Conservancy Home Owners Association. The Burke Centre Conservator is the monthly newsletter that the home owners association uses to keep in communication with the members. The newsletter is mailed out each month to all residents living in Burke, those residents living outside of Burke, and others who have a subscription to the newsletter.
Scope and Content
The Burke Centre Conservator newsletter collection documents the monthly activities of Burke Centre, such as elections, programs and festivals.
The only series in this collection is titled newsletter. The series contains the monthly newsletter, the Burke Centre Conservator, from 1977 to 1993. Also in the series are seasonal programs of events, directory, rules and regulations, Architectural Review Board (ARB) Guidelines Revision Meeting minutes, and other documents. The majority of the collection is the monthly newsletter. The series is contained within four boxes.
Arrangement
Organized into one series.
Series 1: Newsletters, 1977-1993 (Boxes 1-4)
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
The Special Collections and Archives also holds the Planned Community Archives and other personal papers and organizational records that document Reston, Virginia, and other planned communities.
Index Terms
Geographical Names:
Burke (Va.)
Subjects:
Community newspapers--Virginia--Burke.; Housing--Virginia--Burke.
Contents List
- Series 1: Newsletters, 1977-1993; (4 boxes)
  The series contains the monthly newsletter, the Burke Centre Conservator. Also in the series are seasonal programs of events, directory, rules and regulations, Architectural Review Board (ARB) Guidelines Revision Meeting minutes, and other documents.
  - Rules and Regulations, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    414.2
  - Burke Centre Conservator, January 31, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    414.3
  - Burke Centre Conservator, February 28, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    414.4
  - Burke Centre Conservator, March 31, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    414.5
  - Burke Centre Conservator, April 30, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    414.6
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May 31, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    414.7
  - Burke Centre Conservator, June 30, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    414.8
  - Burke Centre Conservator, July 31, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    414.9
  - Burke Centre Conservator, August 31, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    414.10
  - Directory Fall, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    414.11
  - Burke Centre Conservator, September 30, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    414.12
  - Burke Centre Conservator, November 30, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    414.13
  - Burke Centre Conservator, December 31, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    414.14
  - Burke Centre Conservator, January 31, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    414.15
  - Burke Centre Conservator, February 28, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    414.16
  - Burke Centre Conservator, March 31, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    414.17
  - Burke Centre Conservator, April 30, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    414.18
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May 31, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    414.1
  - Burke Centre Conservator, June 30, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    414.19
  - Burke Centre Conservator, July 31, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    414.20
  - Burke Centre Conservator, August 31, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    414.21
  - Burke Centre Conservator, September 30, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    414.22
  - Burke Centre Conservator, October 31, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    414.23
  - Burke Centre Conservator, November 30, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    414.24
  - Burke Centre Conservator, December 31, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    414.25
  - Burke Centre Conservator, January 30, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    414.26
  - Burke Centre Conservator, February 29, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    414.27
  - Burke Centre Conservator, April 30, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    414.28
  - Spring Program, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    414.29
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May 31, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    414.30
  - Burke Centre Conservator, June 30, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    414.31
  - Burke Centre Conservator, July 31, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    414.32
  - Burke Centre Conservator, August 31, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    414.33
  - Burke Centre Conservator, September 30, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    414.34
  - Burke Centre Conservator, October 31, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    414.35
  - Burke Centre Conservator, December 14, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    414.36
  - Burke Centre Conservator, January, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    414.37
  - Burke Centre Conservator, February, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    414.38
  - Burke Centre Conservator, April, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    414.39
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    414.40
  - Burke Centre Conservator, June, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    414.41
  - Burke Centre Conservator, July, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    414.42
  - Burke Centre Conservator, August, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    414.43
  - Burke Centre Conservator, September, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    414.44
  - Burke Centre Conservator, October, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    414.45
  - Burke Centre Conservator, November, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    414.46
  - Burke Centre Conservator, December, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    414.47
  - Burke Centre Conservator, January, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    415.1
  - Winter Program, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    415.2
  - Architectural Guidelines Revised, January, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    415.3
  - Burke Centre Conservator, February, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    415.4
  - Burke Centre Conservator, March, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    415.5
  - Burke Centre Conservator, April, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    415.6
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    415.7
  - Burke Centre Conservator, June, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    415.8
  - Burke Centre Conservator, July, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    415.9
  - Burke Centre Conservator, August, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    415.10
  - Fall Program, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    415.11
  - Burke Centre Conservator, September, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    415.12
  - Burke Centre Conservator, October, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    415.13
  - Burke Centre Conservator, November, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    415.14
  - Burke Centre Conservator, December, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    415.15
  - Burke Centre Conservator, January, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    415.16
  - Burke Centre Conservator, March, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    415.17
  - Burke Centre Conservator, April, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    415.18
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    415.19
  - Burke Centre Conservator, June, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    415.20
  - Burke Centre Conservator, July, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    415.21
  - Burke Centre Conservator, August, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    415.22
  - Burke Centre Conservator, September, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    415.23
  - Burke Centre Conservator, October, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    415.24
  - Burke Centre Conservator, November, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    415.25
  - Burke Centre Conservator, December, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    415.26
  - Burke Centre Conservator, January, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    415.27
  - Candidates For Board of Trustees, February, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    415.28
  - Burke Centre Conservator, February, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    415.29
  - Burke Centre Conservator, March, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    415.30
  - Burke Centre Conservator, April, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    415.31
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    415.32
  - Burke Centre Conservator, July, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    415.33
  - Burke Centre Conservator, September, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    415.34
  - Burke Centre Conservator, November, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    415.35
  - Burke Centre Conservator, December, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    415.36
  - Burke Centre Conservator, January, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    416.1
  - Burke Centre Conservator, February, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    416.2
  - Burke Centre Conservator, March, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    416.3
  - Burke Centre Conservator, April, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    416.4
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    416.5
  - Burke Centre Conservator, June, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    416.6
  - Burke Centre Conservator, August, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    416.7
  - Schedule of Classes Fall, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    416.8
  - Burke Centre Conservator, September, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    416.9
  - Burke Centre Conservator, October, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    416.10
  - Burke Centre Conservator, November, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    416.11
  - Burke Centre Conservator, December, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    416.12
  - Burke Centre Conservator, January, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    416.13
  - Burke Centre Conservator, February, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    416.14
  - Burke Centre Conservator, March, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    416.15
  - Burke Centre Conservator, April, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    416.16
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    416.17
  - Burke Centre Conservator, July, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    416.18
  - Burke Centre Conservator, August, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    416.19
  - Burke Centre Conservator, September, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    416.20
  - Burke Centre Conservator, October, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    416.21
  - Burke Centre Conservator, November, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    416.22
  - Burke Centre Conservator, December, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    416.23
  - Burke Centre Conservator, January, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    416.24
  - Burke Centre Conservator, February, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    416.25
  - Burke Centre Conservator, March, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    416.26
  - Burke Centre Conservator, April, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    416.27
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    416.28
  - Burke Centre Conservator, June, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    416.29
  - Burke Centre Conservator, July, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    416.30
  - Burke Centre Conservator, August, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    416.31
  - Burke Centre Conservator, September, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    416.32
  - Burke Centre Conservator, October, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    416.33
  - Burke Centre Conservator, November, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    416.34
  - Burke Centre Conservator, December, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    416.35
  - Burke Centre Conservator, January, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    416.36
  - Burke Centre Conservator, February, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    416.37
  - Burke Centre Conservator, March, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    416.38
  - Burke Centre Conservator, April, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    416.39
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    416.40
  - Burke Centre Conservator, June, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    416.41
  - Burke Centre Conservator, July, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    416.42
  - Burke Centre Conservator, August, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    416.43
  - Burke Centre Conservator, September, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    416.44
  - Burke Centre Conservator, October, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    416.45
  - Burke Centre Conservator, November, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    416.46
  - Burke Centre Conservator, December, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    416.47
  - Burke Centre Conservator, January, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    417.1
  - Burke Centre Conservator, February, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    417.2
  - Burke Centre Conservator, March, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    417.3
  - Burke Centre Conservator, April, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    417.4
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    417.5
  - Burke Centre Conservator, June, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    417.6
  - Burke Centre Conservator, July, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    417.7
  - Burke Centre Conservator, August, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    417.8
  - Burke Centre Conservator, September, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    417.9
  - Burke Centre Conservator, October, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    417.10
  - Burke Centre Conservator, November, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    417.11
  - Burke Centre Conservator, December, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    417.12
  - Burke Centre Conservator, January, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    417.13
  - Burke Centre Conservator, February, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    417.14
  - Burke Centre Conservator, March, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    417.15
  - Burke Centre Conservator, April, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    417.16
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    417.17
  - Burke Centre Conservator, June, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    417.18
  - Burke Centre Conservator, July, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    417.19
  - Burke Centre Conservator, August, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    417.20
  - Burke Centre Conservator, September, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    417.21
  - Burke Centre Conservator, October, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    417.22
  - Burke Centre Conservator, November, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    417.23
  - Burke Centre Conservator, December, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    417.24
  - Burke Centre Conservator, January, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    417.25
  - Burke Centre Conservator, February, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    417.26
  - Election Issue, March, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    417.27
  - Board of Trustees, April, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    417.28
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    417.29
  - Burke Centre Conservator, June, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    417.30
  - Burke Centre Conservator, July, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    417.31
  - Burke Centre Conservator-August, August, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    417.32
  - Burke Centre Conservator, September, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    417.33
  - Burke Centre Conservator, October, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    417.34
  - Burke Centre Conservator, November, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    417.35
  - Burke Centre Conservator, December, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    417.36
  - Burke Centre Conservator, January, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    418.1
  - Burke Centre Conservator, February, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    418.2
  - Burke Centre Conservator, March, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    418.3
  - Burke Centre Conservator, April, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    418.4
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    418.5
  - Burke Centre Conservator, June, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    418.6
  - Burke Centre Conservator, August, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    418.7
  - Burke Centre Conservator, September, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    418.8
  - Burke Centre Conservator, October, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    418.9
  - Architectural Review Board (ARB) Guidelines Revision Meeting, November, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    418.10
  - Burke Centre Conservator, December, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    418.11
  - Burke Centre Conservator, February, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    418.12
  - Burke Centre Conservator, March, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    418.13
  - Burke Centre Conservator, April, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    418.14
  - Burke Centre Conservator, May, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    418.15